Guide to the Stanford Stories Collection SC1279
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Stories Collection
2015
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
SC1279
12705 megabyte(s)
Arrangement
Stanford Stories participants are listed alphabetically in the finding aid by last name. Alumni class graduation years are indicated as provided. In the event of multiple interviewees, all names are indexed.
Conditions Governing Access
Unless otherwise indicated, materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Scope and Contents
The Stanford Stories collection consists of brief oral histories provided by current Stanford students and Stanford alumni. Oral histories are recorded in person by Stanford University Archives staff, or are contributed as voice recordings via the Stanford Stories telephone line (415-952-7241).
Select video recordings are available on Stanford University Libraries YouTube channel, under the "Stanford University Archives: Stanford Stories" playlist.
Student life.; Stanford alumni; College students -- California; Oral histories.
- Abend, C. Josh (Class of 1950), 2015
- Aguiar, Josias (Class of 2005), 2015
- Ailes, Gabrielle (Class of 2011), 2015
- Alexander, Shelley (with Chun, Anne-Marie "Punky") (Class of 2011), 2015
- Arty, Patricia (with Bhat, Nit) (Class of 2010), 2015
- Bacon, Kimberly (with Basnett, Kaitlyn Makanaakua) (Class of 2015)
- Basnett, Kaitlyn Makanaakua (with Bacon, Kimberly) (Class of 2015)
- Bentz, Michael (Class of 1980, MS 1981), 2015
- Berg, Patricia Donovan (Class of 1955), 2015
- Beyer, Betsy (with Gardner, Erin) (Class of 2005), 2015
- Bhat, Nit (with Arty, Patricia) (Class of 2010), 2015
- Blewitt, Kim (Class of 1992), 2015
- Brown, Alyssa (with Nolff, Jordan) (Class of 2012), 2015
- Brown, Warren (Class of 1955), 2015
- Burgenbauch, Susan (Class of 1965), 2015
- Burke, Bernard (Class of 1958), 2015
- Burke, Eleanor George (Class of 1960), 2015
- Chun, Anne-Marie "Punky" (with Alexander, Shelley) (Class of 2011), 2015
- Chun, Judy (Class of 1981), 2015
- Corrin, Lois (Class of 1975), 2015
- Diaz, Juan Carlos Ochoa (Class of 2005), 2015
- Dillard, Mary (Class of 1990), 2015
- Elliot, Stuart (Class of 1949), 2015
- Esquibel, Daniel Martin "Marty" (Class of 1990), 2015
- Firestone, Kimball (Class of 1955), 2015
- Frazier, Laurel (Class of 2014), 2015
- Fried, Katja (Class of 1995), 2015
- Funkhouser, Ray (Class of 1960), 2015
- Gardner, Erin (with Beyer, Betsy) (Class of 2005), 2015
- Green, Ann (with Green, George) (Class of 1962), 2015
- Green, George (with Green, Ann) (Class of 1960), 2015
- Griffing, Edward (Class of 1955), 2015
- Harine, Angela Parizek (Social class of 1964, class of 1985), 2015
- Hemphill, Marka Davis (Class of 1960), 2015
- Hill, David (Class of 1953), 2015
- Holman, Dean (Class of 1951, MBA 1952), 2015
- Ibarra, Juan (1995), 2015
- Kensek, Craig (Class of 1980), 2015
- Kingham, Sallie Cross (Class of 1965), 2015
- Kulic, Nuri (Class of 1950), 2015
- Lara, Irene (Class of 1995), 2015
- Mendoza, Ali Katrina (Class of 2010), 2015
- Mendoza, Jerilyn Lopez (Class of 1990), 2015
- Merrill, David (with Sheng, Amy) (Class of 2000), 2015
- Michaelson, Hal (Class of 1971), 2015
- Miller, Carol Ann Newman (Class of 1970, MD 1975), 2015
- Moguel, Walter (Class of 1990), 2015
- Morgan, David (Class of 1965), 2015
- Mosley, Michael (Class of 2000), 2015
- Nolff, Jordan (with Brown, Alyssa) (Class of 2012), 2015
- Paige, Christopher (Class of 1965), 2015
- Paige, Tina Duncan (Class of 1965), 2015
- Perez, Mary (Class of 2005), 2015
- Phan, Quynh (Class of 2010), 2015
- Price, Dirk (Class of 1985), 2015
- Price, Peggy Wynn (Class of 1945), 2015
- Reeves, Darryl (Class of 2005), 2015
- Richau, Joshua (Class of 1995), 2015
- Robinson, Sylvia Evans (Class of 1970), 2015
- Sanford, Linda (Class of 1975), 2015
- Schmidt, Peter (Class of 1965), 2015
- Shelton, Adrian Millar (Class of 1970), 2015
- Sheng, Amy (with Merrill, David) (Class of 2000), 2015
- Skougaard, Mary Hill (Class of 1950), 2015
- Smith, Daniel C. (Class of 1966, 1971), 2015
- Smith, Hilary (Class of 1990), 2015
- Steil, Peter (Class of 1965), 2015
- Stella, Rebecca Flores (Class of 1990), 2015
- Sy, Lolita (with Sy, Stephen) (Class of 1983), 2015
- Sy, Stephen (with Sy, Lolita) (Class of 1984), 2015
- Syka, John (Class of 1980), 2015
- Tanner, Carol Scilacci (with Tanner, Douglas) (Class of 1975), 2015
- Tanner, Douglas (with Tanner, Carol Scilacci) (Class of 1975), 2015
- Tennant, Patricia Figone (Class of 1970), 2015
- Terman, Terence (Terry) (Class of 1952), 2015
- Torre, Jim (Class of 1965), 2015
- Trachta, Jon (with Trachta, Pam Hale Lochhead) (Class of 1965), 2015
- Trachta, Pam Hale Lochhead (with Trachta, Jon) (Class of 1965), 2015
- Vahan, Ellen Thayer (Class of 1965), 2015
- Van Vleck, Kenneth (Class of 1990), 2015
- Ward, Michael (Class of 1990), 2015
- Weisgerber, Kathleen Orsini (Class of 1965), 2015
- Wilson, Bruce (Class of 1950), 2015
- Wong, Denis (MBA 1954), 2015